morevisas.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy of MoreVisas | MoreVisas Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

At Morevisas we strive to provide transparency through our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is written in a way to be compliant with the recent European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). While the GDPR is a European law, we are taking this opportunity to clarify and apply our privacy policy to everyone, no matter where you're located. Our privacy policy and terms and conditions may change from time to time and the clients should keep checking our website frequently to be updated. Our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account unless stated otherwise.

**TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED:**

We collect personal information about our users in order to provide our products, services, and customer support. Our products, services, and customer support are provided through many platforms including but not limited to: websites, phone apps, email, and telephone. The specific platform and product, service, or support you interact with may affect the personal data we collect.

In some situation users may provide us with personal information without us asking for it, or through means not intended for the collection of particular types of information. Whilst we may take reasonable steps to protect this data, the user will have bypassed our systems, processes, and control and thus the information provided will not be governed by this privacy policy.

In some situations users may provide us personal information over platforms that are outside our control; for example through social media or forums. Whilst any information collected by us is governed by this Privacy Policy, the platform by which it was communicated will be governed by its own Privacy Policy.

**HOW THE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED:**

**Information that you specifically give us**

While you use our products and services you may be asked to provide certain types of personal information. This might happen through our website, applications, online chat systems, telephone, paper forms, or in-person meetings. We will give you a Collection Notice at the time, to explain how we will use the personal information we are asking for. The notice may be written or verbal.

We may request, collect, or process the following information:

  * Account Details - password
  * Contact Details - email address, phone number
  * Location Details - physical address, billing address, timezone
  * Identity Details - full name, proof of identity (e.g. drivers licence, passport), proof of address (e.g. utility bill)
  * Financial Information - credit card details, wire transfer details, payment processor details (e.g. skrill, paypal), tax numbers
  * User Generated Content - transaction descriptions, transaction attachments

**Information that we collect from others**

Users have the ability to start a transaction with non-users by providing contact details such as email address, physical address, and phone number. In these situations, the information will be collected and stored by us to contact the non-user and to prevent abuse of our systems.

Your payment provider may transmit information about the payment that we may collect or process.

In some situations, personal information of users may be collected from public sources.

We may collect or process the following information:

  * Contact Details - email address, phone number
  * Location Details - Physical Address, billing address, timezone
  * Financial Information - transaction details, payment account details (e.g. paypal email address and physical address), wire transfer details
  * User Generated Content - transaction description

Our partners may create transactions on your behalf, in these situations the information that can be provided is the same as the information we may request, collect and process from individual users. Whilst our partners platforms will be governed by their own privacy policy, any personal information that is transferred to our platform will be treated and protected as though it was submitted by a user.

**Information we collect as you use our service**

We maintain records of the interactions we have with our users, including the products, services and customer support we have provided. This includes the interactions our users have with our platform such as when a user has viewed a page or clicked a button.

When we are contacted we may collect personal information that is intrinsic to the communication. For example, if we are contacted via email, we will collect the email address used.

**Links to other sites**

On our website, you may encounter links to third party websites. These links may be from us, or they may appear as content generated by other users. These linked sites are not under our control and thus we are not responsible for their actions. Before providing your personal information via any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that website and its privacy policy.

**HOW IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION USED:**

The information we request, collect, and process is primarily used to provide users with the product or service they have requested. More specifically, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * to provide the service or product you have requested;
  * to facilitate the creation of Service Agreements between you and the company;
  * to answer enquiries about our services, or to respond to a complaint;
  * to promote our other programs, products or services which may be of interest to you (unless you have opted out from such communications);
  * to comply with legal and regulatory obligations;
  * if otherwise permitted or required by law; or
  * for other purposes with your consent, unless you withdraw your consent for these purposes.

The 'lawful processing' grounds on which we will use personal information about our users are (but are not limited to):

  * when a user has given consent;
  * when necessary for the performance of a contract to which the user is party;
  * processing is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations;
  * processing is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of our users or of another natural person;
  * processing is done in pursuing our legitimate interests, where these interests do not infringe on the rights of our users.

**WHEN WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION :**

We recognize the importance of preserving integrity and maintaining confidentiality. Any personal information and/or business proprietary material that are disclosed will be kept highly confidential.

All information given to Morevisas by its prospective clients, is kept strictly confidential and on a need-to-know basis and is well protected. We record your personal details only if you send us a message. You can be assured that your personal information is used only by our trained staff for the work purpose that you engaged us to do.

We will not use your e-mail address for any purpose, and not disclose it without your permission. Your information is never used for marketing or solicitation and is never sold or given to anyone for these purposes.

Morevisas never supplies any other person or organization with your information except those government agencies involved in your immigration process (e.g. Australian Immigration Authorities, DIBP or the Home office, UK, etc.).

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalogs or updates on our new services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless we receive your consent.

Keeping with the times our site features an online payment service which operates on the lines of Morevisas fraud protection policy to ensure our clients a hassle-free payment.??The site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We encrypt your personal and financial information and use our best efforts to prevent it from being read or intercepted as the information travels over the Internet. While we are committed to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In case the user has any complaint (s) regarding our services or processes then he/she can approach us and get registered the same.

**Other disclosures and transfers**

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties for the following purposes:

  * if necessary to provide the service or product you have requested;
  * We receive court orders, subpoenas or other requests for information by law enforcement,
  * if otherwise permitted or required by law; or
  * for other purposes with your consent.

As we are a global company, with offices around the world, your personal information may be processed by staff in any of our offices. Morevisas currently has head office in India.

**ACCESSING OR CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You have the right to request access to the personal information Morevisas holds about you. Unless an exception applies, we must allow you to see the personal information we hold about you, within a reasonable time period, and without unreasonable expense for no charge. Most personal information can be accessed by logging into your account. If you wish to access information that is not accessible through the platform, or wish to download all personal information we hold on you in a portable data format, please contact our Privacy Officer.

You also have the right to request the correction of the personal information we hold about you. All your personal information can be updated through the user settings pages. If you require assistance please contact our customer support.

**EXERCISING YOUR OTHER RIGHTS**

You have a number of other rights in relation to the personal data Morevisas holds about you, however, there may be restrictions on how you may exercise the rights. This is largely due to the nature of the products and services we provide. Much of the data we collect is in order to check your eligibility for the service.

**Morevisas Complaints**

If you have an enquiry or a complaint about the way we handle your personal information, or to seek to exercise your privacy rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you, you may contact our Privacy Officer as follows:

For the purposes of the GDPR, our Privacy Officer is also our Data Protection Officer (DPO).
